Good morning," said the little prince.
"Good morning to you said the railway switchman please tell me What do you do here?"
the little prince asked.
"I saw out Travelers in bundles of a thousand," said the switchman
and I said and off the trains that carry him now to the right, now to the left."
And a brilliantly lighted express train shook the switchman's cabin as it rushed
by with a roar like thunder.
"They are in a great hurry," said the little prince.
"What are they looking for?"
"Not even the locomotive engineer knows that," said the switchman.
And a second brilliantly lighted express thundered by, in the opposite direction.
"Are they coming back already?"
demanded the little prince.
"These are not the same ones," said the switchman. "It is an exchange."
"Were they not satisfied where they were?"
asked the little prince.
"No one is ever satisfied where he is," said the switchman. And they heard the
roaring thunder of a third brilliantly lighted express.
"Are they pursuing the first Travelers demanded the little prince.
"They are pursuing nothing at all," said the switchman.
"They are asleep in there, or if they're not asleep they are yawning.
Only the children are flattening their noses against the window panes
Only the children know what they are looking for the little prince.
"They waste their time over a ragdoll and it becomes very important to them;
and if anybody takes it away from them, they cry..."
"They are lucky," the switchman said